http://www.brothersfour.com/privacy_policy#privacy_policy

The Brothers Four
close
HomeAboutAbout the GroupBob Flick InterviewMark PearsonMike McCoyKarl OlsenBob FlickMusicThe Brothers Four RenewalBeautiful World of The Brothers FourIn the Name of BrotherhoodMerry Christmas Expanded EditionGolden AnniversarySilver Anniversary ConcertGreenfields & Other GoldThis Land Is Your LandThe Tokyo TapesAll MusicBuy NowTour DatesPress KitContact
Privacy Policy
Personal Information Collected by this Web Site - Mailing ListThis web site includes an opt-in mailing list. You may signup using only your email address, or you can optionally also provide your name and geographic area, as well as message options. Geographic information is used to limit the number of mailings you get from me; mailings of local interest are sent only to people in a specific geographic area unless you have indicated that you wish to receive all messages. In addition, if you purchase something from my online store, you are automatically added to the mailing list, with your full address. Every message I send contains an unsubscribe link at the bottom; if you wish to leave the mailing list, you can click on this link and you will be removed immediately (no manual effort involved). This mailing list is never shared with anyone else. It is stored in a secure database, and is available only to me.
Personal Information Collected by this Web Site - Online Store
If you purchase from my online store, we collect the information needed to process that purchase, and store the information in a secure database. In addition to your name, address and email, this includes additional contact information (phone number, optionally), and the required credit card information. If you ship your purchase to an address other than your billing address, and/or to another person, we also store that name and address. We keep this information for the duration specified by US laws, and do not share it with anyone else. The store operates under the storerevenue.biz domain name.
Geolocation
This site uses server side geolocation to determine the country from which you are accessing the site. We use this information so that we can comply with the EU Cookie Laws, and also use it occasionally to show links of interest to people in your country, rather than US links. We do not do anything to associate you as an individual with this country information. (See our section on Cookies below, for information on how we save this information).
Anonymous Information Collected on this Web SiteAnonymous data is collected on server logs to enable analysis of web site activity, and debugging of active code. It can also be used to provide aggregate statistics about visitors and usage. You, as an individual user, remain anonymous. Such data may include pages visited, your IP address, browser type, how you landed, whether via search engine results, referral, or a direct link, and how long you stayed. Such data is used for analysis of web site effectiveness, and to identify possible areas for improvement. Cookies
We plan to use Google Analytics to collect information about the use of our website, although as of this date (5/16/2018) it is not yet included. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics normally collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We went one step further and specified "IP addredss anonymization" to mask your real IP address. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Service and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser.
This web site uses third party advertising companies to serve ads. This includes Google and Amazon. These third parties may serve content and advertisements, collect information directly from visitors, and place or recognize cookies on visitors' browsers. Google uses a DoubleClick DART cookie to
serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Google, click here. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.Amazon ads also place cookies; you can read about Amazon's Interest Based Ads here.We also use Skimlinks to link to ticket sales websites, and to other merchants in a few instances. Skimlinks uses cookies and collects user data. You can see their privacy policy here.YouTube normally places cookies when a website, such as this one, shows YouTube videos on our own pages. These videos are shown by YouTube, and the cookies they place, associated with our site, are the same ones they would place if you visited their site to view the video. We have chosen the YouTube option that instructs them to not save cookies when you are on our site, as long as you don't press the "Play" button to view the video. If you don't want YouTube to set cookies, then don't start the video. If you start it, that is considered "consent" to their cookies.
You can opt out of advertising from certain companies at these two websites:
the DAA opt-out program (currently available here) and the NAI opt-out program (currently available here).
Our own site uses cookies to keep track of visitors in the EU who have approved the use of cookies; we also save your country information in a cookie if you have allowed cookies. The cookies we use for this purpose are iseucountry, thiscc and euconsent. As always, our own store uses session cookies which are not saved permanently, and are required in order to do e-commerce.
